<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-03-05T12:33:57+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//feed.xml</id><title type="html">Anirudh Kaushik</title><subtitle>Undergraduate Researcher at CVIT, IIIT Hyderabad. Working on Medical Image Analysis and Computer Aided Diagnosis with Prof. Jayanthi Sivaswamy. Founder and Co-ordinator of IIIT Society of Applied Quantum Computing </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Blind Priestess</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Blind-Priestess/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blind Priestess"/><published>2025-03-05T11:51:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-05T11:51:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Blind-Priestess</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Blind-Priestess/"><![CDATA[<div class="background-wrapper" data-bg="/assets/img/blind_priestess.png"> <div class="content-container"> A strange scent, diffused light, muted as it passed through the lids of her closed eyes. She turned her head and smiled. The click of the key turning in its lock, the sound of the door opening. She stood and felt the back of her chair. The scent, the soft thuds which approached her. Flowers, the scent gave them away. A gift. She pretended to be surprised, the soft smile never leaving her. It grew wider as their fingers brushed in the exchange. The shuffling of packages, the opening of lids, the scent of food. She felt the back of the chair and sat down once more. She tracked with her sightless gaze, following the movements around the kitchen. The prattling about the day, the clinking of cutlery, the sock-clad thuds on the linoleum. She placed her hands on the table as she received the warm plate, the cutlery gently placed in her palms. She leaned down till she could feel the heat of the meal on her chin. The chattering continued as they both ate. The fork searching for her lips to prevent the sting of the sauces and the condiment. A bit too harsh for her preference but she rarely complained. The cutting of meat and the soft chewing of closed lips, she could feel it in her left ear, mixing with the adorable voice she loved. She ate at a slower pace and she could feel the patient waiting in the voice, dinner was not the focus. She set her fork down and placed the knife besides it. A napkin gently dabbed her smiling lips and she could feel the warm of the delicate fingers that tended to her. The plates were cleared and a hand found hers. The anticipated familiarity of the warmth. As it pulled her closer, she inhaled. A strange scent, unfamiliar, but not unkind. A weariness. Her brows furrowed. She leaned in closer till her nose felt the warmth of their neck and inhaled once more. But the scent had passed and she felt the faithful warmth as it guided her to their place of rest. The tales continued, in her right ear, the kind lilt of their voice, the heat of their uncalloused palm in her hand. She felt the bed sink in as she sat down and she waited for it to sink in again. The air was colder here and it only made her wait for their warmth that much longer. She tapped her fingers on the mattress as she felt the breathing grow closer, till it finally joined her. She laid down and closed her already shut eyes. A blanket wrapped around her shoulders and then was adjusted at her back. She felt a satisfied nod near her as the mattress shifted. She was pulled closer and anchored at the waist and it made her blush. A content sigh behind her and the soft weight on her lulled her to sleep. </div> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about homely routines]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Splintered Marionette</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Splintered-Marionette/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Splintered Marionette"/><published>2025-02-25T22:02:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-25T22:02:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Splintered-Marionette</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2025/Splintered-Marionette/"><![CDATA[<p>The old puppet sat on the attic floor, leaning against a box, just out of reach of the sunbeam from the single attic window. She waited patiently for the sun to dip. As the subbeam retreated towards the wall, she began to twitch until finally, it was nighttime.</p> <p>She stood on shaky legs and brushed off the dust that had settled on her. Her mouth opened and closed with a clicking sound as she adjusted her rusty mechanisms. She walked by an old mirror and lifted the white sheet that covered it to reveal it’s cracked surface. She gave an approving nod to her appearance, a little worse for wear since she last saw herself, but beautiful nonetheless.</p> <p>She lumbered over towards the door, her movements becoming more graceful with every step she took. Her wooden arms extended and slid in between the door and it’s frame and pulled it open with a strength which belied her small frame.</p> <p>She sat on the edge of each stair, swinging her legs downwards and bending her knees with the jump, the rusty iron of her joints squeaking with each step. Finally, she escaped the attic, making way to the bedchambers.</p> <p>The door to the little boy’s room was slightly ajar, he slept gently, as little boys should. She stood atop his cradle, gazing down at the infant’s sleeping form, his sleep-touseled hair flowing like dulled gold, his breathy cadence the only sound which evidenced the life inside him.</p> <p>She leaned down and cruelly poked his cheek, his rosy skin sinking like a marshmallow as the warmth of his body seeped through the puppet’s wooden fingers. She pulled back. No, he was not to blame, she thought and turned to the other rooms.</p> <p>She entered the parent’s room, the mother slept alone in bed and the father was nowhere in sight. She sighed but was not deterred. She crept up on the bed, the rusty creaking of her joints the only indication of her presence. She felt the mother’s hair slip through her wooden fingers like golden silk, so unlike her own, which were woven from dark horse-hair. She felt her own coarse strands and seethed with rage.</p> <p>She marched with purposeful strides across the bed and climbed onto the dresser. She levered her legs in the drawer and pushed it open. She returned with a large scissor, the weight of it throwing her off-balance as she held it with both hands. She opened it’s jaws and brought them down several times till the bed was littered with sangria-golden strands. She would smirk if she could, but her painted countenance bore no emotion.</p> <p>The living room and parlour had changed little since she last saw them. Her painted sandals clicked as she sauntered to the ornate Gramophone and placed a vinyl atop it’s surface. She adjusted the arm and pushed the button as the disk began to spin. When no sound played, her painted face was unable to frown. The arm was missing it’s needle. She seethed with rage, her fists clenching at her sides as her painted face remained the same. She kicked the wooden box as it spun it’s disk. A thumbtack came into view and she stuck it in the arm and adjusted it once more. The record screeched as if in pain and the puppet covered her painted ears till she could finally take no more and turned the gramophone off. She shook her head. There would be no dancing tonight, she thought and made her way to the parlour.</p> <p>Her wooden hands searched the ashtray till she found a half stub and she lit it, sitting with it and taking a puff which never came. Nevertheless, it calmed her and she threw the rest away.</p> <p>As the first rays of dawn broke the night, she rushed up the attic stair, sparing one parting glance to the sleeping infant’s cradle. She would spend more time with him next time, when he was older.</p> <p>She took her place in the dust mould and leaned back against the box as the sunbeam began to creep up.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about a marionette doll]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Her House</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Her-House/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Her House"/><published>2024-12-27T19:16:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-27T19:16:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Her-House</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Her-House/"><![CDATA[<p>The little child sat under the hammock. It was a March afternoon, and the meadow near his house was in full bloom in shades of bright yellow and red and violet. Fluffy white clouds moved slowly against the warm blue of the sky. He quietly sipped from a glass of lemonade, too big for his grip and too bitter for his taste as he lounged under the hammock, a gentle spring breeze carrying the pollen straight to his nose. He sneezed but there was no one to say “bless you” and his heart clenched. He ate from a packet of nuts, assorted and roasted, leaving out the wallnuts. The ice in the lemonade melted slowly and the afternoon changed colors to orange.</p> <p>He stood up and carried himself inside and locked the doors. He marched to his bedroom, his steps slow and sluggish, oddly relaxed. No one told him to brush his teeth or wash his face. He sunk into his pillows, his eyes glancing at the mural in his room as he drifted to sleep. The morning was cold and dull and gray. He made his way to the dining hall but no one cooked in the kitchen. The air was crisp and quiet as he sat down at the table. His gaze fell to the kitchen, missing the familiar silhouette. He made himself some toast with jam and honey and a dollop of butter. He added six spoons of sugar to his hot chocolate and sat down on the couch.</p> <p>The tele hummed and moaned but he paid no attention to the sounds, the couch felt empty without the familiar weight. He ate slowly, the sugar and the sweet not providing even an ounce of relief. He made his way to the bath, staring at the bubbles as the tub filled. The scent of bath salts mixed with the steam filled the air, turning everything foggy. He dipped himself in like a tea bag a few times before sinking beneath the surface. He turned up the temperature but still felt cold. He lay inside till his body shriveled up like a prune.</p> <p>He stepped out the tub and there was no warm, fluffy towel waiting for him. He patted and wiped his pale milky skin and brushed and combed his smooth blonde hair. There were no clothes waiting for him on the bed and he sighed. After dressing, he poured himself some lemonade and a bowl of roasted nuts and made his way outside. It was yet another beautiful noon, the meadow bloomed as he sat underneath the hammock, but it did not swing. The familiar lump in the hammock replaced by a taut emptiness. He made his way back inside.</p> <p>He went to a room and unlocked it. It opened with a pop, the interiors untouched, left as they had been. He took in the scent, breathing deeply, holding the air in his lungs for as long as he could. He made his way to the closet and pulled out a sundress, carrying it to the bay window. He curled up in the sun beam as he took in its scent, his eyes fluttering shut as he murmured softly, “mama” and drifted to sleep.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about an 8-year-old boy living by himself]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A rather pleasant evening</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/A-rather-pleasant-evening/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A rather pleasant evening"/><published>2024-12-18T16:27:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-18T16:27:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/A-rather-pleasant-evening</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/A-rather-pleasant-evening/"><![CDATA[<p>She sat alone in the library, reading at an excruciatingly slow pace. Her movements were deliberate and calculated to cause maximum discomfort to herself. She sat with her ankles folded under her at odd positions, her eyes uncomfortably far from the reading material, her back slouched till she resembled a snail, her neck strained till it formed an L. Her fingernails scratched at the pages like chalk on board making uncomfortable sounds which gave her goosebumps and made her toes curl up.</p> <p>Her appearance was delicate, her eyes sharp and curious, her nose slim, her skin fair and smooth and her hair soft and neatly braided, freshly washed and fragrant. She had a cup of piping hot tea next to her as she read, letting her fingers burn on the cup for as long as she could. She sipped the tea without blowing first, letting it gently burn her tongue and throat as she swallowed. She read slowly, making sure to read each word over and over again.</p> <p>After several agonizing hours she got up, pinching her legs which felt like they were filled with powdered glass. Her mind felt a soft buzz and she stood and made her way to her room. Her house was quiet, the breathy cadence of her parents asleep, the soft snoring of her infant brother in his cradle and the quiet hum of the refrigerator.</p> <p>She went to the washroom in her room to brush and wash her face. She bristled her gums with the hard unkempt brush taking care to make sure they bleed and itch. She squeezed lemon juice into her mouth and then grinded her teeth, her toes curling up so hard she almost pulled out a tile, the goosebumps so severe despite the lack of body hair, she looked like a hedgehog.</p> <p>She flossed her gums, ensuring the thin thread digs into her soft, sensitive hums as she flossed them mercilessly. Soft whimpers echoed in the bathroom as she flossed, spitting out blood and saliva.</p> <p>Finally, she rinsed and began to wash her face. She used hot water to dry out her skin and then didn’t moisturize, letting her face feel dry and hard. She did the same for her wrists, the dryness almost unbreable for her pretty and angelic fair skin. The girl made her way to bed.</p> <p>She let her bangs fall over her eyes as she undid her braids. She carefully brushed her hair, ensuring they’re tangled in just the right way. She preheated her pillow and laid down on the warm side. She pulled up her blanket just below where she’d like to have it. She pulled up her pyjamas till they crumpled around her calves and felt the creases on her knee gap and calves.</p> <p>She adjusted the thermostat till it was warmer than she’d like and fell asleep, making sure her back would ache next morning.</p> <p>It rained outside her window the entire night, the heavens weeping in silent protest as the guardian angel assigned to this particular girl pulled at his hair and grinded his teeth due to a lifetime of observing her. He begged and pleaded God to relieve him of his duty and God, unable to watch his son in misery, looked away.</p> <p>The girl woke up the next day and made her way to do her routines, her guardian angel banging his head on every wall as he floated behind her. The girl got dressed for school, making sure her socks were loose and damp, her shoes bit her feet, and the large amounts of lemon juice she had on an empty stomach gave her an ulcer.</p> <p>Her mother smiled sweetly at her as she left and her dad gave her a loving hug while her infant brother simply cooed a loving goodbye. The girl waved goodbye and left, her guardian angel floating behind, banging his head on the stairs and then on the door and lastly in the driveway.</p> <p>As soon as the girl stepped on the street, a large truck hit her, the guardian angel had a mild concussion and was slow to react, unable to protect her. He was severed from her instantly for the girl had died. He floated along aimlessly.</p> <p>He arrived at a garden, the october sun casting an orange glow on the trees as the afternoon melted away. The cool breeze bit sharply at him as he rested under a tree. His head felt heavy but he felt peaceful. His body ached but he felt at ease. He slowly began to disappear as the evening faded, muttering a soft “Thank you” under his breath as he rejoined the stars.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about a guardian angel to a girl with an unpleasant habit]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Everything Stew</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Everything-Stew/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Everything Stew"/><published>2024-07-06T16:31:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-07-06T16:31:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Everything-Stew</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Everything-Stew/"><![CDATA[<p>The pot gurgled and fizzed with the occassional whistle. A heavy aroma filled the air. In the hollow of a tree, a delicate hand stirred a giant pot, only stopping to add more ingredients. Diced, minced, grated, puréed and mashed, they were promptly tossed into the pot and the aroma became thicker and richer. Finally, the hand stopped and scratched its chin. Something was missing. A nose breathed deeply. Maybe a spice? perhaps a carrot? A fish head? “ughk” a mouth in the corner of the hollow twisted in disgust. No fish heads.</p> <p>A head popped from the hollow of the tree, a golden ponytail followed in pursuit. Two wings emerged, like that of an insect and in haste ran off. The fairy escaped, forsaking her stew. A mouth in the corner of the hollow twisted further.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about cooking stew~]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Two at a Time</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Two-At-A-Time/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Two at a Time"/><published>2024-07-01T14:42:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-07-01T14:42:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Two-At-A-Time</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Two-At-A-Time/"><![CDATA[<p>No matter how much she tried, her little legs just won’t stretch that far. She couldn’t climb the steps two at a time. She begged her father to teach her, a man who could climb 3 steps with a single lunge. He told her that climbing more than one step at a time was not very lady like and that she should put her foolish ambitions to rest. But the girl was no giver upper. However determined she may be, she was no fool, jumping on the stairs was forbidden. The only way forward was to stretch and grow her legs.</p> <p>Everyday the girl would stretch. She asked the local farmers to tie her legs to their horses and pull but all she got was a whack. When hard work didn’t work, the girl resorted to prayer and offered her younger brother but the gods did not lend her their ear.</p> <p>One night, a monster crept into the girls’ basement. The monster heard a little girl of 10 receive a scolding from a man of 40 for “wasting electricity”. The door swung open and the little girl made her way down the stairs and towards the light. The monster readied itself. As soon as the light went out, the monster dashed towards the girl. The girl ran, the monster chased. The girl began climbing the stairs one at a time, and the monster climbed them two at a time.</p> <p>The girl knew that she would be caught if she didn’t do something. She jumped! She leapt and covered 3 stairs, becoming faster than the monster. But the forbidden rule was broken. The house roared and shrieked. Two hands popped out and lifted the porch up, as if lifting its pants. The house got up and left, leaving behind a staircase which led to no floor, a girl and a monster.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about a rebel who loses her home]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Think, Thank, Thought</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Think-thank-thought/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Think, Thank, Thought"/><published>2024-04-15T06:16:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-15T06:16:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Think-thank-thought</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2024/Think-thank-thought/"><![CDATA[<p>Sleeping. Sleeping. Waking up to a strange ceiling. Messy routines and then school. At school, she once again drifted off and before she knew it she was back home. She blinked and it was night time. She decided to brush her teeth. A pretty face smiled at her from the mirror which made her blush. She thought about it as she walked to her bed in her fluffy slippers, her mouth feeling minty fresh. She laid her head on the pillow and wondered about the person in the mirror and all of a sudden it was morning.</p> <p>She moved slowly down the stairs, her fluffy slippers on her feet. She rubbed her eyes and yawned and found herself answering a question in class. She asked to go to the washroom in hopes of finding the girl who had smiled at her. She opened the door to the girls washroom but found her self back at home instead. She removed her shoes and walked to the kitchen. She passed by the calendar which told her it was friday. Her mother was cooking her favourite stew. She sat down at the table and watched as her mom stirred the pot.</p> <p>“How was school today?”</p> <p>“The usual”</p> <p>“What about that boy you’re always talking about”</p> <p>“He’s also fine, I guess”</p> <p>“You two had a fight?”</p> <p>“I don’t think so?!?”</p> <p>The girl stretched her arms and legs at the same time and let out a big exhale. She opened her eyes to her mother and her brother greeting their father at the door. “I brought that juice you wanted to try from that new store that we passed by last saturday”, “Ah, thank you”, “It comes in a glass bottle and everything, you can share it with your brother in your room. I have something to discuss with mom”</p> <p>The girl walked up to the room, her fluffy slippers make soft thuds as she climbed the steps two at a time. Her little brother followed on all fours. She poured him a glass and one for herself. She opened the window and a cool summer breeze filled the room. Her brother asked her for some more juice and she handed him the bottle. She sat on a cushion and she watched her brother greedily suck on the bottle. Only a little while before she could meet the girl from the mirror.</p> <p>She heard loud noises coming from below, her parents. She could hear her mother sobbing. Just a few more minutes till 9pm. Her mother entered the room and picked up the little boy and carried him away. The bottle lay on the ground in a puddle of juice. The girl walked to the washroom and switched on the light, it was bright and it hurt her eyes. She stood infront of the sink, still no sign of the girl. She brushed and brushed till her gums bled, still no sign of the girl. Finally, she gave up and turned to return.</p> <p>Out of the corner of her eye, she caught a faint smile and it made her heart pound. She felt a smile of her own spread across her face. She lay on the bed, blushing. As she turned to face the wall, she found it was already morning.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about the suppressed alter of girl with DID]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The King of the Mountain</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/King-of-the-mountain/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The King of the Mountain"/><published>2023-11-02T14:42:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T14:42:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/King-of-the-mountain</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/King-of-the-mountain/"><![CDATA[<p>A little girl sat in her room, alone, listening to music. She was sad, for today she had been forced to eat no less than 3 carrots during lunch. She barely had any space left for dessert and very reluctantly parted with the remaining piece of cake. She decided to hole up in her room and listen to music as a form of silent protest. However, it was not a silent protest and her parents found it obnoxious.</p> <p>The girl had good grades in school, was atheletic and could be considered decently pretty. What then, was her vice because of which she found herself in such an unfavourable circumstance. After her brain failed to solve this conundrum, the girl resorted to throwing tantrums. However, the loud music was a cause for concern.</p> <p>The parents went to reason with the girl, one at a time, they bribed her with jewellery and they threatened her with flagellation, but the girl stood her ground. Her parents had no choice, on a winter night such as this one, they simply couldn’t risk their lives because of a teenager’s angst. They did the only sensible thing and went out to dinner.</p> <p>As soon as her parents left, the girl stopped her loud music. The parent’s noticed this but it was already too late, they had to hurry for a reservation had already been made. On a cold and dark night such as this one, a disturbance attracted monsters, one in particular was very frightening.</p> <p>This monster caused all other monsters to tremble with fear. Locked doors and prayers cannot keep him away. All that can be done is to wish that he never notices you. As midnight drew nearer, the girl grew restless, her parents should’ve been back by now. No one picked up her calls either. She could not sleep without her hot chocolate. Alas, she decided to make it herself.</p> <p>She heated the milk in a pot and melted the chocolate in a pan. Then she mixed them both together and added two spoons full of sugar just to be safe. She sat down with her beverage and waited for sleep to arrive. Instead, she heard loud thuds outside, and a low grunting sound. The girl looked out her window and noticed the white snow and the moonless sky had been replaced with a feathery blackness.</p> <p>“Feathery”, why did that word come to her mind, she wondered just as the blackness moved away, only to bend down and look through the window. Two red eyes peered at her, the monster had come.</p> <p>It was the king of the mountain, he was as tall as he was wide, with long legs folded into a squat. With his long boney finger he beckoned the girl to the window, for he could not enter the house. The girl obeyed but not before finishing her drink with two big gulps.</p> <p>The king stared at the girl and the girl stared back, not a word was said. Finally, the king broke what was becoming an awkward silence “What is it that smells so sweet? Is it you or some other meat? If so …” Before he could finish his rhyme, the girl let out a burp so nasty, yet so delicious that the king froze.</p> <p>A delicate aroma filled the king’s nose and made its way into his lungs from where it spread through his entire body. He had never smelt anything so deliciously sweet yet so awfully pungent. What could have produced such an aroma? He grabbed the girl and took her with him. He cut her open to find the sweet hot chocolate with two spoons of sugar inside her stomach, but there was something else… Three boiled carrot floated in the dark brown liquid.</p> <p>The king drank his fill and was overcome with the most lovely feeling. A most relaxing sleepiness overtook him as he sank into his bed which felt softer than ever. His eyes drooped and he fell into dream-filled slumber.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Writing"/><category term="Stories"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A short story about a petulant girl and her unsavory beverage]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Reze</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/reze/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reze"/><published>2023-10-28T21:41:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T21:41:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/reze</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/reze/"><![CDATA[<p>Reze from chainsawman. Subject by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CvWDN0vJWbe/">inoitoh</a></p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_subject-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_subject-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_subject-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/reze_subject.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Subject, A sketch by inoitoh </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/reze.jpeg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> final sketch </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_contrast-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_contrast-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/reze_contrast-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/reze_contrast.jpeg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Contrast enhanced </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Art"/><category term="Sketching"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainsawman Girls (4/4), Reze]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quanxi</title><link href="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/quanxi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quanxi"/><published>2023-10-26T16:32:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T16:32:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/quanxi</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anirudhkaushik2003.github.io//blog/2023/quanxi/"><![CDATA[<p>Quanxi from chainsawman. Subject by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CvONKJ_SJBZ/?hl=en">inoitoh</a></p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_subject-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_subject-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_subject-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/quanxi_subject.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Subject, A sketch by inoitoh </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/quanxi.jpeg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> final sketch </div> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="mx-auto d-block"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_contrast-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_contrast-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/quanxi_contrast-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/quanxi_contrast.jpeg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="auto" height="auto" data-zoomable="" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Contrast enhanced </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Art"/><category term="Sketching"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainsawman Girls (3/4), Quanxi]]></summary></entry></feed>